Use your best judgment.
(Sheldon:)Well, I think I have a
nice 2009 AnaMantle HC.
(Sheldon:)It's usually indicated for
acutely inflamed hemorrhoids,
(Sheldon:)but it also goes nicely
with non-mucosal body parts.
(Leonard:)Sounds great.
(Sheldon:)Excellent choice.
Okay, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Come on, come on, come on.
(Sheldon:)Priya?
(Priya:)Good morning, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)For shame, Leonard, for shame.
(Sheldon:)And to think,
(Sheldon:)I was ready to waste
(Sheldon:)the last of my good
hemorrhoid cream on you.
(Leonard:)Making pretty
good time, huh?
(Sheldon:)Is that really what you want
to talk about, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)What do you want to talk about?